BRUNO CODINHA

IT STUDENT

@ bruno.codinha@tecnico.ulisboa.pt

**** +351910477440

♀ Lisbon, Portugal

github.com/SkyVandal

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Veertly

Ctober 2020 - January 2021

React | Git

Git Javascript

 Developer in a mid-sized team on a virtual event platform for a startup.

Research Intern

INESC-INOV

July 2020 - September 2020

• Developer in a scrum team, in the main research center for Computer Science and Engineering in Portugal.

Mentor

NAPE-IST

July 2020 - Present

 Supported students in their academic journey and developed tools to aid their studies.

Collaborator

IFFF

May 2019 - Present

• Developer on an international organization in a multitude of initiatives to aid student's performance.

Software Engineer

High Creativity

April 2017 - Present

HTML Javascript

• Currently leading the development of the website highcreativity.pt.

PROJECTS

YARIS

🛗 July 2020 - September 2020

Docker REST API

 Worked as a software developer on a project to support the maritime operations in the Gulf of Guinea. It is expected to be used by up to 3500 professionals.

Cryptocurrency Tool

Abril 2020 - Present

Python Java Linux

• Developer of automation tools to trade cryptocurrencies and system administrator of dedicated servers.

CS IEEE Repository

May 2019 - Present

C/C++

• Maintainer of a widely used codebase for supporting University's students on projects.

ABOUT ME

My goal is to envision and conceive tools that can aid solving human's largest challenges.

I see myself both as a practical engineer and a devoted craftsman. I have been in touch both with Software and Science since an early age, coding on my own and researching endless documentaries and articles.

I come from a very multicultural background and have a wide range of interests, from blues music and football to competitive chess and classic literature.

LANGUAGES

| Portuguese | | |
|------------|--|--|
| English | | |
| French | | |
| Spanish | | |

EDUCATION

M.Sc. in Computer Science and Engineering **Instituto Superior Técnico**

Espt 2020 - ongoing

B.Sc. in Computer Science and Engineering Instituto Superior Técnico

Sept 2017 - ongoing

International Highschool

European School of Brussels II